A Brief Survey Of Deep Reinforcement Learning
A Survey Of Approaches Combining Safety And Security For Industrial Control Systems
A Survey Of Distributed Optimization And Control Algorithms For Electric Power Systems
A Survey Of Dynamic Positioning Control Systems
A Survey Of Intrusion Detection On Industrial Control Systems
A Survey Of Multi-Agent Formation Control
A Survey On Analysis And Design Of Model-Based Fuzzy Control Systems
A Survey On Cpg-Inspired Control Models And System Implementation
A Survey On Modeling, Biofuels, Control And Supervision Systems Applied In Internal Combustion Engines
A Universal Multidisciplinary Design Optimization Platform For Aircraft- Dipasda
A Wheelchair Control System Using Human-Machine Interaction: Single-Modal And Multimodal Approaches
Adaptive Control Schemes For Improving The Control System Dynamics: A Review
Adaptive Control Strategies For Interlimb Coordination In Legged Robots: A Review
Adaptive Critic Nonlinear Robust Control: A Survey
An Overview Of Dynamic Linearizationbased Data-Driven Control And Applications
An Overview On Flight Dynamics And Control Approaches For Hypersonic Vehicles
Closing The Loops An Industrial Perspective On The Present And Future Impact Of Control
Computational Methods In Optimization Considering Uncertainties – An Overview
Control Frameworks In Network Emulation Testbeds: A Survey
Control Methods For Internet-Based Teleoperation Systems: A Review
Control Of Connected And Automated Vehicles State Of The Art And Future Challenges
Control Strategies For Crane Systems- A Comprehensive Review
Control Strategies For Soft Robotic Manipulators: A Survey
Cortical Control Of Arm Movements: A Dynamical Systems Perspective
Dc Microgrids—Part I: A Review Of Control Strategies And Stabilization Techniques
Distributed_Networked_Control_Systems:_A_Brief_Overview
Disturbance-Observer-Based Control And Related Methods—An Overview
Energy Performance Optimization In Buildings: A Review On Semantic Interoperability,Faultdetection,And Predictivecontrol
Formal Methods For Control Synthesis: An Optimization Perspective
Hierarchical Control And An Overview Of The Control And Reserve Management Strategies
Human–Agent Teaming For Multirobot Control: A Review Of Human Factors Issues
Hybrid Metaheuristics In Combinatorial Optimization: A Survey
Integration Of Electric Vehicles In Smart Grid: A Review On Vehicle To Grid Technologies And Optimization Techniques
Introduction To Feedback Control Of Underactuated Vtol Vehicles
Manual Control Cybernetics: State-Of-The-Art And Current Trends
Mas-Based Distributed Coordinated Control And Optimization In Microgrid And Microgrid Clusters: A Comprehensive Overview
Model Predictive Control Of High-Power Modular Multilevel Converters—An Overview
Model Predictive Control Of Ph Neutralization Processes- A Review
Model Predictive Control Recent Developments And Future Promise
Modeling And Control Of Cyber-Physical Systems Subject To Cyber Attacks: A Survey Of Recent Advances And Challenges
Networked Control System: Survey And Directions
On The Contribution Ofwind Farms In Automatic Generation Control: Review And New Control Approach
Optimal Process Control
Overview: Collective Control Of Multi-Agent Systems
Regularization And Bayesian Learning In Dynamical Systems: Past,Present And Future
Reinforcement Learning And Adaptive Dynamic Programming For Feedback Control
Review Of Applications Of Fuzzy Logic In Multi-Agent-Based Control System Of Ac-Dc Hybrid Microgrid
Review Of Control Strategies For Robotic Movement Training After Neurologic Injury
Review Of Modelling And Control Of Two-Wheeled Robots
Review Of Optimization Strategies For System-Level Design In Hybrid Electric Vehicles
Review On Control Techniques And Methodologies For Maximum Power Extraction From Wind Energy Systems
Robot Control Overview: An Industrial Perspective
Simple Adaptive Control - A Stable Direct Model Reference Adaptive Control Methodology - Brief Survey
Simulation-Based Approaches For Verification Of Embedded Control Systems
Stochastic Model Predictive Control:An Overview And Perspectives For Future Research
Surface Roughness Optimization Techniques Of Cnc Milling: A Review
Survey Of Visual And Force/Tactile Control Of Robots For Physical Interaction In Spain
Survey On Iterative Learning Control, Repetitive Control, And Run-To-Run Control
Survey On Recent Advances In Networked Control Systems
The University Of Texas Atarlington Autonomous Aerial Vehicle An Overview
Theory And Applications Of Hvac Control Systems - A Review Of Model Predictive Control
Token-Based Pull Production Control Systems: An Introductory Overview
Vision And Control For Uavs: A Survey Of General Methods And Of Inexpensive Platforms For Infrastructure Inspection