 
Review of Optimization Strategies for System-Level Design in Hybrid Electric Vehicles
Review of modelling and controlof two-wheeled robots
The University of Texas atArlington Autonomous Aerial Vehicle An Overview
Survey of Visual and Force/Tactile Control of Robots for Physical Interaction in Spain
Model predictive control Recent developments and future promise
An overview on flight dynamics and control approaches for hypersonic vehicles



Energy performance optimization in buildings:A review on semantic interoperability,faultdetection,and predictivecontrol  
Modeling and control of Cyber-Physical Systems subject to cyber attacks: A survey of recent advances and challenges   
Token-based pull production control systems: an introductory overview
DC Microgrids—Part I: A Review of Control Strategies and Stabilization Techniques
An Overview of Dynamic LinearizationBased Data-Driven Control and Applications
Networked Control System: Survey and Directions
Integration of electric vehicles in smart grid: A review on vehicle to grid technologies and optimization techniques
Robot Control Overview: An Industrial Perspective



A Survey of Distributed Optimization and Control Algorithms for Electric Power Systems
A Universal Multidisciplinary Design Optimization Platform for Aircraft- DIPasda
A survey of dynamic positioning control systems
Control Strategies for Soft Robotic Manipulators A Survey
Formal Methods for Control Synthesis: An Optimization Perspective
Stochastic Model Predictive Control
A survey of approaches combining safety and security for industrial control systems
 Model predictive control of pH neutralization processes- A review
Control of Connected and Automated Vehicles State of the Art and Future Challenges 
Control strategies for crane systems- A comprehensive review
Simulation-Based Approaches for Verification of Embedded Control Systems



Adaptive Control Strategies for Interlimb Coordination in Legged Robots: A Review
Review of Applications of Fuzzy Logic in Multi-Agent-Based Control System of AC-DC Hybrid Microgrid
MAS-Based Distributed Coordinated Control and Optimization in Microgrid and Microgrid Clusters: A Comprehensive Overview
Stochastic model predictive control:an overview and perspectives for future research
Surface Roughness Optimization Techniques of CNC Milling: A Review
Vision and Control for UAVs: A Survey of General Methods and of Inexpensive Platforms for Infrastructure Inspection
Optimal Process Control
Human–Agent Teaming for Multirobot Control: A Review of Human Factors Issues
A survey of multi-agent formation control
